# Praise Oyedele

Akure, Ondo, Nigeria



opra.temmy@gmail.com



08129334848



linkedin.com/in/praise-oyedele-207226198

## **Summary**

Meet Praise a young, creative, and multi-skilled fellow. He specifies in the creation of beautiful and fascinating logos (3D, 2D & minimalist). Been tech-savvy, he engages in designing a responsive website, Onsite SEO, recommendation of hosting services, etc. With his pool of experiences, he can help detect slacks, proffer solutions and help businesses and organizations gain their ground and trust with their customers again. He has intriguing marketing strategies that allow converting perspective into paying customers. As such, you can trust him to help you with your marketing gigs and other things like your logo design and your website design in full from scratch.

### **Experience**



### Web Developer

Climax Group

Sep 2021 - Present (5 months +)

# Web Developer

Fiverr

Mar 2020 - Present (1 year 11 months +)

**Web Designer** 

Pison Books

Nov 2017 - Aug 2021 (3 years 10 months)

#### **Education**



### Federal University of Technology Akure

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science

Dec 2019 - Nov 2023

Meet Praise a young, creative and multi-skilled fellow. He specifies in creation of high attractive and fascinating logos (3D, 2D & minimalist). Been a tech-savvy he engages in creation of responsive website, Onsite SEO, recommendation of hosting services etc. With his pool of experiences, he is able to help detect slacks, proffer solutions and help business and organization gain their ground and trust with their customers again. He has intriguing marketing strategies that helps convert perspective into paying customer as such you can trust him with helping you with your marketing gigs.

#### baptist high school, ila Orangun

SSCE. Science Sep 2009 - Jul 2015

# Federal University of Technology Akure

# Undergraduate, Computer Science

# **Skills**

Web Development • Computer Graphics Design • WordPress • User Experience Design (UED) • PHP • JavaScript • Responsive Web Design • Adobe Photoshop • Front-End Development • Graphic Design